<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Cosmic Kitty</title>
    <link>/blogs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Cosmic Kitty</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 19:46:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/blogs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>To End Plastic Production Forever. </title>
      <link>/blogs/toendplastic/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 19:46:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/toendplastic/</guid>
      <description>January 18, 2021 THE CHANGE.ORG PETITION THAT REFUSES TO LOAD. I WILL TRY AGAIN TOMORROW. “What does it mean to function as a group in a changing environment? How can we organize ourselves intentionally to combat the imbedded isolation of late capitalism? … I believe collaboration is natural and can be reclaimed…” (Alexis Paulin Gumbs, [Undrowned Black Feminist Lessons from Marine Mammals](https://www.akpress.org/undrowned.html, page 51) According to [Condor Ferries](https://www.condorferries.co.uk/plastic-in-the-ocean-statistics, “there is now 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eye Contact</title>
      <link>/blogs/eyecontact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 19:39:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/eyecontact/</guid>
      <description>January 18, 2021 Until white folk understand something fundamental about their – I’m reading the introduction of “Undrowned Black Feminist Lessons from Marine Mammals” by Alexis Pauline Gumbs – thank you Nina for the suggestion – and realizing that whiteness – the white person – the white skinned – light skinned – human – the person thing who is not dark skinned – so me – until the ‘we’ and the ‘they’ realize that the ‘our’ and the ‘their’ safety, security, 401k and Robinhood account is tied up in the endangerment of dark skinned humans…an understanding of something – what that thing is – seeking comfort in the midst of radicalized America…an escape route somewhere – unavoidable – the ‘our’ and the ‘their’ lives are protected in a way that does not travel the exact same way as it does for dark skinned person – the word thing – doesn’t even apply – doesn’t even jolt the same way – because objectification has been normalized – who is white America a slave to?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Vagus Nerve</title>
      <link>/blogs/thevagus/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 19:34:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/thevagus/</guid>
      <description>January 17, 2021 An analogous legion Quelling with desire I send my friend Nina from North Carolina some money to buy a chair for her back – In return, she sends me a book written by a cantadora – Today I opened the windows and
Threw – flung- scattered- bird seed from the palm my mother made in her womb I threw the seeds at the men who gathered below Across the platform, they stood inert as I bellowed coarsely plundering my throat from the top floor – Reconfigure this room and disinfect the floors with a yellow and green sponge Space to breathe I chew on the insides of my mouth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trauma is a Strengthening Tool when Transmuted with Intention. </title>
      <link>/blogs/traumais/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 19:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/traumais/</guid>
      <description>January 15, 2021 “Be your higher self to get the work done. Stop Forgetting. Remember why you’re here.” This morning on Clubhouse in a room called “Breakfast with Champions: The Millionaire Breakfast Club”, I was listening to Brian Culhane, Myron Golden and Akemi Sue Fisher discuss wealth creation and brand management, where they draw inspiration from and other ways or staying motivated enough to do the work and to keep showing up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kuleana</title>
      <link>/blogs/kuleana/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 19:21:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/kuleana/</guid>
      <description>January 14, 2021 Today was Plastic Play Wednesday #6 (I still owe myself #5 – I skipped last weeks to go for a run in the sun that was much needed) Today we talked about Limu Koku, an edible seaweed featured in the picture above, ancient practices of tattooing in Hawai’i after one survives a volcanic eruption (as Susan did in 2019) and what it means to be a care taker of one’s environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 New Moon in Capricorn and a Break Up Letter to Unorganized Procrastination: Unveiling the Demonic Time Wasters that No Longer Serve. </title>
      <link>/blogs/2021newmoon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 19:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/2021newmoon/</guid>
      <description>January 13, 2021 “GREATNESS AND COMFORT DO NOT GO TOGETHER” – CATHY HELLER
Sept 29, 2020 Where am I really from? Micah’s belly. What if everyone’s experience of reality is a religion? The moment of being in awe of another for extended periods of time leads to idolization – in the act of that, we forget ourselves and our godliness. This is why everyone has their own code where their religion becomes what one folds one’s life around.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love plastic</title>
      <link>/blogs/loveplastic/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 19:06:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/loveplastic/</guid>
      <description>January 12, 2021 Plastic is an organism. It carries a particular energetic materiality. It holds history and transportation routes; knowledge in its very essence. Plastic was once a good thing. It was loved and adored by all. The creators of it were deemed heroes and geniuses. everyone was happy. But then something happened. To pin point exactly would be to lose sight of the whole picture – by zooming in, the rest gets observed in our hidden knowing – object permanence – we know the rest of the map exists but we can’t see it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Now – Temporality of “The Moment” – An Indicator of Nervousness and Anxiety Induced Trauma of Not Knowing What Comes Next. </title>
      <link>/blogs/now-temp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 19:02:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/now-temp/</guid>
      <description>January 11, 2021 What Does It Mean To Be A Friend, Now*? The Now – aspect – the silent auras circulate – two honks and a dirty engine – it takes a calm refusal to smooth out the roughness – a fluid sway in the body – mechanical rumblings of the M train – a flash back memory to that movie Michelle recommended – Snowpiercier – around and around in ice and snow until until until – go watch the movie – Cockroaches – last night I flushed one into the toilet bowl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Afternoon I Cried for Etel</title>
      <link>/blogs/thisafternoon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 18:59:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/thisafternoon/</guid>
      <description>January 9, 2021 “For me, the pain of dying is going to be the impossibility of visiting that site one more time.” – Etel Adnan A cloud around my auto pilot love aura – not for you – yet – more – in between – the stagnation of last time- bumping up against what we do not know and being okay with the pain is questionable – is love enough ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank You Clubhouse</title>
      <link>/blogs/thankyouclubhouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 18:46:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/thankyouclubhouse/</guid>
      <description>January 9, 2021 In no particular order, these are the links to medical professionals and start ups who are experimenting with psychedelic treatment as a technique to cure alcoholism, depression, and PTSD, tech fellowships, DJ Tools, podcasts about music and music making, a book about gifted adults, exclusive ad-free music, and queer movie reviews. Clubhouse is my new favorite thing. I have Randy to thank for telling me about it, and Sabio for the invite.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Anti-Aesthetic: Inconsistency as resistance to normalized hyper-productivity (and why that is a good thing) </title>
      <link>/blogs/theantiaesthetic/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 18:38:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/theantiaesthetic/</guid>
      <description>January 7, 2021 Boards with neon colors grabbing our attention, mine, maybe yours, with their symmetrical configurations, like Monday, the organizational tool. There are recognizable tendencies and patterns within the spheres of digital marketing and advertising, where one learns codified manipulation tactics to induce desire. Sacred geometry implored for diapers, a work out mirror, $3000 bedsheets. I forget where the phrase “aesthetics will kill you” comes from. The fight is on to see how far I will use these skills to make things better for the rest of the world starting with the women and young girls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magic mondays</title>
      <link>/blogs/magicmondays/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 18:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/magicmondays/</guid>
      <description>Originally posted January 5, 2021
Today felt like a dream. I went to bed at 430am on Sunday and woke up at 7am to read for a bit, Micah woke me up and I couldn’t go back to sleep again. I must have fallen back asleep at 830am and when I woke up it was 1pm. I haven’t slept like that in a really long time. There were dreams about old friends, making up, forgiveness and some type of traveling expedition where I was a host consoling one of my old friends in Singapore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thaumatrope</title>
      <link>/blogs/thaumatrope/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 18:23:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/thaumatrope/</guid>
      <description>Originally posted January 4, 2021
It’s the first Monday of the year 2021. The Moon is waning gibbous in Virgo. I already lost my no sugar goal by consuming three fried Oreos from Tony’s after confronting a thought I had earlier this morning that I was going to die within the next two years. I am only mildly concerned about this download because so far, my predictions about certain things have been accurate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy New Rotation Around and Sun; men are not the enemy, capitalism is.</title>
      <link>/blogs/happynewroration/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 18:19:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/happynewroration/</guid>
      <description>Originally posted January 2, 2021.
Today I made: Vegan Peanut Butter Orange Chocolate Banana Bread
Dry: 1 Cup (any type of Flour) Cinnamon to taste Cloves to taste Orange peel to taste Baking powder Baking soda Salt Wet: 1 Cup Apple Sauce 1/4 Silk almond milk 1/4 Peanut Butter 1/4 Brown Caster Sugar 1/4 cup diced Endangered Species Chocolate, Oat Milk Rice Crisp + Dark Chocolate, 55% Cocoa Mash 3 super ripe bananas together and add it to the wet ingredients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oden warns of a missing toe</title>
      <link>/blogs/oden/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 18:17:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/oden/</guid>
      <description>Originally posted December 29, 2020
my attention. Creating cycles around an already circular platform of thought. Guitar picking. Somber wanting. Touching sensitively the grass looking forward to lunch. Started the yin yoga week with Kasandra – Tuesday is orange – sacral, made orange French toast – bread from the Mexican bakery down the road, the owner let me off with $1.50 debt – they picked two cards – realizing how with the current situation in the world, people are choosing to go inward to answer the questions they pick for themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Birds</title>
      <link>/blogs/birds/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 15:47:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/birds/</guid>
      <description>Listen to my Album &amp;ldquo;BIRDS&amp;rdquo; everywhere you find music including bandcamp </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Moon in Aries</title>
      <link>/blogs/newmoon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 15:44:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/newmoon/</guid>
      <description>Listen to my Album &amp;ldquo;New Moon in Aries&amp;rdquo; everywhere you find music including bandcamp </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everything Is Pencil</title>
      <link>/blogs/everythingispencil/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 15:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/everythingispencil/</guid>
      <description>Listen to my Album &amp;ldquo;Everything is Pencil&amp;rdquo; everywhere you find music including bandcamp </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Liberatory Learners</title>
      <link>/blogs/aboutliberatorylearners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 10:03:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/aboutliberatorylearners/</guid>
      <description>What is Liberatory Learners? Liberatory Learners is a space for interdisciplinary play designed to investigate, in a personalized way, each student’s individual curiosities about their world.
Classes incorporate:
 Minecraft Film Vegan Culinary Arts Creative Thinking Literacy Music Movement  Join us Today!    View this post on Instagram         A post shared by Liberatory Learners! (@liberatorylearners)
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instagram</title>
      <link>/blogs/instagramliberatorylearners/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 10:11:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/instagramliberatorylearners/</guid>
      <description>Latest Post: Benjamin Von Wong is an amazing artist who creates masterful works from plastic waste that as he states on his website, &amp;ldquo;make positive impact unforgettable&amp;rdquo;.    View this post on Instagram         A post shared by Liberatory Learners! (@liberatorylearners)
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Youtube</title>
      <link>/blogs/liberatorylearnersyt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 10:07:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/liberatorylearnersyt/</guid>
      <description>Latest Meeting   Podcast Episode with Gary Dušek   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Titties</title>
      <link>/blogs/abouttitties/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 10:01:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/abouttitties/</guid>
      <description>What is Titties?
Titties For Change is a Research Hub Dedicated to Ending Plastic Production Forever Through the Study of Utopian Ideas, Independent Thought, and the Imagination.
We are based in Brooklyn, New York. We host vegan plastic-less pot lucks and open mics.
We sometimes dance on the street together.
We are anti-war, anti-plastic, vegan art collective that creates hybrid spaces to educate, re-create, entertain, heal, and transform to find long term solutions to plastic production, homelessness, poverty, slavery and war by shifting rhetoric from “impossible” to “possible” by changing the world through expression, creative projects, and community outreach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Titties Blueprint</title>
      <link>/blogs/tittiesblueprint/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 10:00:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/tittiesblueprint/</guid>
      <description>Steps Strategies/steps for eliminating plastic waste     1 Create a network of those committed to eliminating plastic, homelessness, and associated issues   2 Create a pitch for the concept, the resources needed, and the founder   3 Turn empty commercial spaces into hubs for community action   4 Gather important political, business, and non-for-profit figures behind the community space concept   5 Holding Plastic manufacturers accountable via emails   6 Sell donated plastic waste to fund community aid   7 Make a list of alternative products to advertise, distribute, and partner with   8 Create a grant to buy an alternative organic material to replace their plastic inventory (restaurants)   9 Partner with a list of restaurants   10 Create survey for restaurants to determine their single use plastic needs   11 Advocacy for all the different industries that produce plastics   12 Host events to increase awareness on community issues   13 Partner with a list of businesses to supply the community centers   14 Create collaborative private spaces within the community centers for rent   15 Institute mental health care in community centers   16 Create products made from recyclables to sell and raise money for the community centers   17 Endorse and support art and artists that create publicity and advocacy for these social issues   18 Creation of mobile and web apps to facilitate these processes   19 Create platform for coordinating restaurants   20 Create market for all of the various components   21 Create a plan for investors   22 Make a list of supporting non-for-profits that help fulfill the mission of ending plastic production   23 Get people to sign the petition (investors, politicians, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Past Events</title>
      <link>/blogs/pastevents/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 09:56:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/pastevents/</guid>
      <description>Nov 2018: Tee2Tote events: making totebags and distributing them at a local Bushwick supermarket.
Dec 2019: C3
Jul 2019: Vegan Potluck
May 2019: Tee2Tote Public Event
Oct 2019: Titties Bag Making Workshop Singapore
Jan 2020: &amp;ldquo;The Struggle and The Promise, a vegan potluck art show.
Feb 2020: Calling the Plastic &amp;amp; Plastic Play Zoom Meetings
Sep 2020: Plastic Creatures
Oct 2020: Tote Bag + Open Mic event</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Me For Events</title>
      <link>/blogs/bookme/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 09:53:46 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/bookme/</guid>
      <description>Available for Writing, Music, Modelling, Acting, Workshops, and Speaking Engagements. Link to: Resume
Link to: Resume Page 2</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Directing</title>
      <link>/blogs/directing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 09:39:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/directing/</guid>
      <description>Answers and Questions: Singapore      
Other Works:  Like Mold by Shuana Noone - 2012 When the Fire Starts to Burn by Clare Tassinari - 2012 …Like Sisters - 2014 Talk Radio by Eric Bogosian - 2015 From the Hands of Strange Children - 2015 The American of Wisconsin by John Oluwole ADEkoje - 2016 “Principles of Geometry: Filmic Component” Ms Hannah has Shit to Say Ms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Performance</title>
      <link>/blogs/performance/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 09:23:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/performance/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Who the Fuck is Cho Chang?&amp;rdquo;    Brooklyn Arts Center - 2018
More Performances:
 Brooklyn Arts Center - 2018 Langston Hughes House - 2019 Frequency Collective - 2019  Brooklyn Bazaar - 2019 Wild Project Theatre - 2019 In Singapore during Quarantine - 2020 In Brooklyn during Quarantine - 2020   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thesis</title>
      <link>/blogs/thesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 09:12:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/thesis/</guid>
      <description>“(Between the Streets) In Worcester : Redefining Professional Education in Community Development to Cultivate Empathy through a Community Theatrical Framework” Redefining Professional Education in Community Development to Cultivate Empathy through a Community Theatrical Framework By Chiu Yi Hannah Yukon
This research paper presents an alternative form of conducing Community Development Research. It highlights the gaps that currently exist in professional education with the community development and planning program at Clark University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plays</title>
      <link>/blogs/plays/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 09:11:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/plays/</guid>
      <description>Children&amp;rsquo;s Books and Plays  The Worst Wizard Ever and Other Fairy Tales - Produced at the Worcester Polytechnic Institute in partnership with the Latino Education Institute + students from the Goddard School of Technology - 2015 Peter and the Wolf (An Adaptation) - Produced at the Worcester Polytechnic Institute in partnership with the Latino Education Institute + students from the Goddard School of Technology - 2014 Pillowland WIP  Contact for more information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Series Work</title>
      <link>/blogs/serieswork/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 09:03:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/serieswork/</guid>
      <description>I have written a number of works, with Chapbooks being a focused medium.
 ATOA: A Meditative Poem Through the Alphabet i  Interview   ATOA: A Meditative Poem Through the Alphabet ii Break Up Letters 2018 Break Up Letters 2019 Break Up Letters 2020: Will be out for sale soon.  Find all the work available at Queer-Art.org, Snipfeed.Co, and Square(WIP) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Story Behind Everything is pencil.</title>
      <link>/blogs/mymusicstory/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 08:52:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/mymusicstory/</guid>
      <description>There is still so much I would change on this album. I probably will, sonically at least, some parts stick out in ways that make me cringe, but I said May 6th, which means May 6th. I will need to recover the corrupted files (yes 2 weeks before the completion of this, my laptop &amp;ldquo;couldn&amp;rsquo;t load&amp;rdquo; the original files which made it impossible for Alex to mix and master these tracks the way that a song like BIRDS sounds like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music</title>
      <link>/blogs/music/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 08:21:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/music/</guid>
      <description>Listen to &amp;ldquo;Everything is Pencil&amp;rdquo;  (Youtube)   (Bandcamp) (Spotify) (SoundCloud) (Apple Music) </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
